Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series IX. Events and classes
  - Open Houses, 1988, 1994, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Open House - some slides, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Open House - some slides, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Open House, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Open House, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Zweighalt Dedication, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Annual Conference, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Exhibits, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Exhibits, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Exhibits, 1911 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Students in anatomy (or postmortem) room in James Law Hall with dissected animals on trolleys; Prof. G.S. Hopkins standing under a standing student in center; human and dog skeletons on table at left., 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Rows of students with faculty in front under portico of James Law Hall; James Law seated in center, 1903-05 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 3 rows of students in anatomy lab with Professor G.S. Hopkins in center., 1905 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Veterinary banquet, Feb. 15, 1905, Society of Comparative Medicine, on 10th anniversary of founding of the College., 1905 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 5 rows of students; with faculty in front center: Williams, Hopkins, Gage, Law, ?, Moore; Gift of Mrs. John F. Miller., 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 4 rows of students in suits and jackets in anatomy lab in James Law Hall., 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 2 rows of 12 students in suits. "Gift of Mrs. John F. Milk", 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 4 rows of students in anatomy lab; student on right has a "C" on his sweater; Professor G.S. Hopkins in center front., 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "Veterinary Class of 1907." -- Students at rows of tables in anatomy laboratory of James Law Hall with bones and parts of skeletons., 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 3 rows of students in dark suits in front of ivy covered wall of James Law Hall. "Darby memorabilia given by Arthur North '35", 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "Veterinary Class of 1907" - Students in suits seated on either side of two long tables., 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 3 rows of students in white; with 4 faculty in dark suits in front row; in anatomy lab with a horse skeleton on right., 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 6 rows of students outside under portico of James Law Hall; Florence Kimball is 2nd row, right; James Law is seated with other faculty in front, 1908-11 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 6 rows of students outside under portico of James Law Hall; Florence Kimball is 2nd row, right; James Law is seated with other faculty in front, 1908-11 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "Class of 1910" - 3 rows of 25 students in white outside under portico of James Law Hall; Florence Kimball in seated in white coat; with 2 faculty in center: Hopkins and Sunderville., 1910 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 4 rows of 29 students in white; with 4 faculty under James Law Hall portico: Miller, Hopkins, Sunderville, Frost, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Students in white with caps; a horse is upside down being dissected on the lawn in front of the Clinic buildings., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 4 rows of students in white; 3 faculty in 2nd row in dark suits, under James Law Hall portico., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 3 rows of students in dark suits, 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 4 rows of students in suits., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 4 rows of students in whites; a black dog is in the center; in front of James Law Hall, 1916 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 4 rows of students in white; one student in first row center holding a black dog in front of James Law Hall. ' Photo taken in 1916., 1918-1919 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 4 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1917 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 5 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1917 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 2 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1920 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 2 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1920 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - "Spring 1920" - 2 rows of students in dark suits outside James Law Hall., 1920 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 2 rows of students under James Law Hall portico; with faculty in front center: Udall, Fish, Gage, Moore, Williams, Hopkins., 1921 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 4 rows of students in dark suits; Prof. Donald W. Baker in back row center??, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - "NYS College Class of 1934"; 5 rows of students in whites; Professors Udall and Gibbons in lower right in front of the Clinics building., 1934 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 4 rows of students in whites; with faculty in center in front of Clinic building., 1935 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 7 rows of students in uniform overcoats in snow on steps of Bailey Hall?, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Company C. 2306th S.C.S.U. June 28, 1943-Oct. 16, 1943. Many rows of students in tan military uniforms with Co. C. flag in top center., 1943 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 5 rows of students in Willard Straight Hall., 1944,45,46 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 3 rows of students outside in front of Clinic building; faculty in front row, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 3 rows of students in suits indoors in front of large curtained windows; Dean Hagan seated in front row 4th from left, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - "Class of 1952"; 4 rows of students with faculty in front., 1952 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Large group of students with faculty under James Law Hall portico; Faculty in center include Gage, Williams; James Law is 3rd from left in 2nd row., n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Rows of men and women in ballroom at annual conference 1956 Dr. Francis H Fox on floor at right; Dr. Stephen J. Roberts on right., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 14 young men in uniform?; cross legged person in center holds a football., n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 2 rows of students in whites in front of Hall-Wilson Laboratory, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Students in pathology and bacteriology lab at benches, 1903 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Students in pathology and bacteriology lab at benches with fume hood in ceiling, 1903 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Students in amphitheater in James Law Hall; James Law seated next to Auzouz papier-mache horse model, 1905 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Surgery on a horse with students in white; James Law standing in white brimmed hat in center; Profession W.L. Williams 2nd from left in white cap hat. "Print made from a glass plate.", pre-1908 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Students dissecting horses in anatomy lab, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 14 students in Post-mortem room near James Law Hall, with animal body parts on trolleys., 1902? (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 20 students (include 3 women) in white with kymograph in a physiology class??, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Students studying in periodical reading in Flower Library on 2nd floor of James Law Hall, 1920s (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ambulatory service -- 6 students are examing a pig on its side on a farm call on ambulatory service, 1960s? (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Ambulatory service -- 6 students are examining a pig on its side on a farm call on ambulatory service (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Series X. Faculty and Staff
  - Lists/Directories, 1950-1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lists/Directories, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lists/Directories, 1973-n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Roster of Special Interests, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Code of Ethics, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Position Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Profiles, 1980's-n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Profiles, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Profiles, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Workshop on Teaching, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Senior Faculty Seminars, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Staff Sercice Recognition Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters-"Schurman News and Views", 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "VIP:Veterinary Information for Personel", 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Faculty and Staff Roster, 1975, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Millenium Time Capsule (Box 8)
  - Biographical Files (including photographs)
    - Faculty
      - Centennial faculty (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Abou-Madi, Noha (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Acland, Gregory (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Aguirre, Gustavo (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Ainsworth, Dorothy (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Akey, Bruce (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Andrews, Edwin Joseph (Box 23, Folder 7)
        1941-
      - Antczak, Douglas F. (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Appel, Max J. (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Appel, Max J. (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Appleton, Judith (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Asmus, Henry (Box 23, Folder 12)
        1875-1939
        See also Memorial Statement
      - Avery, Roger (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Babish, John (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Baggs, Raymond (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Bailey, Michele M. (Smith) (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Baines, Joel N. (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Baker, Donald Wyckoff (Box 23, Folder 18-19)
        1899-1978
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History collection (Ep Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Baker, Donald Wyckoff (Box 23, Folder 20)
        Oversized photo
      - Baker, James Andrew (Box 23, Folder 21)
        1910-1975
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326
      - Baker, James Andrew (Box 23, Folder 22)
        Items were removed from a scrapbook created by Jeannie Griffith
      - Baldwin, Charles (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Ball, Barry (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Barr, Margaret (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Barr, Stephen Charles (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Barrett, Robert B. (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Bell, Robin G. (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Benner, James W. (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Benson, Thomas F. (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Bentinck-Smith, John (Box 23, Folder 31)
        1919-2005
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Memorial Statement
      - Bergman, Emmett Norlin (Box 23, Folder 32)
        1929-1989
      - Beyenbach, Klaus (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Birch, Raymond Russell (Box 23, Folder 34)
        1881-1959
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-525; Memorial Statement
      - Bistner, Stephen Ira (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Blue, Julia Tait (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Blue, Murray (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Bolton, Gary Robert (Box 23, Folder 38)
        1942-1982
      - Bowman, Dwight D. (Box 23, Folder 39-40)
      - Bowser, Paul R. (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Boyer, Clyde I., Jr. (Box 23, Folder 42)
        1913-2003
      - Brasmer, Timothy H. (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Brooks, Marjory (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Brown, H. Alex (Box 23, Folder 45)
        1960-
      - Bruner, Dorsey William (Box 23, Folder 46)
        1906-1996
      - Brunett, Earl Louis (Box 23, Folder 47)
        1898-1943
      - Brunner, Michael Arthur (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Brunson, David B. (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Bunch, Sharon (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - Buckles, Elizabeth L. (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Burnett, Samuel Howard (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Calnek, Bruce Wixson (Box 23, Folder 53-54)
        1932-
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History collection 24-4-3349; Papers 24-2-3346
      - Campbell, Samuel Gordon (Box 23, Folder 55-56)
        1933-1997
      - Carlisle, James G. (Box 23, Folder 57)
        1930-
      - Carmichael, Leland E. (Box 23, Folder 58-61)
        See also Papers 24-4-3388
      - Casarett, Alison P. (Box 24, Folder 1)
        1930-2002
      - Casey, James W. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Castleman, Benjamin (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Center, Sharon A. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Center, Sharon A. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Cerione, Richard A. (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
      - Chang, Yung-Fu (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Cho, Jane (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Clark, Lawrence (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Cockerell, Gary L. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Coggins, Leroy (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Cole, Randall Knight (Box 24, Folder 13)
        1912-2006
        See also Oral History collection 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Collier, Michael A. (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Collins, Ruth N. (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Comar, Cyril L. (Box 24, Folder 16)
        1914-1979
      - Concannon, Patrick W. (Box 24, Folder 17)
        1941-2015
      - Cook, Vanessa L. (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Coonrod, Scott (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Cooper, Barry J. (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Corradino, Robert A. (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Cowen, B. (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Cummings, John Francis (Box 24, Folder 23-25)
        1936-1996
      - Cypess, Raymond H. (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Daels, Peter (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Danks, Arthur Gordon (Box 24, Folder 28)
        1906-1989
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection (EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Davidson, ? (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Davisson, Robin L. (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - DeBoy, Jack (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Delahanty, Donald Dee (Box 24, Folder 32)
        1923-1975
      - de Lahunta, Alexander (Box 24, Folder 33-37)
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3349; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - de Noronha, Fernando (Box 24, Folder 38)
        1924-2010
      - Dhupa, Nishi (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Dietert, Rodney R. (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Dill, Stephen G. (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Dillingham, Lloyd (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Dinsmore, Paige (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Divers, Thomas J. (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Dobson, Alan (Box 24, Folder 45-46)
        1928-
      - Dougherty, Ellsworth (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Dougherty, Robert W. (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Dubovi, Edward J. (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - Ducharme, Normand Guy (Box 24, Folder 50)
        1957-
      - Dukes, Henry Hugh (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
        1895-1987
        See also Papers 6640: Oral History Collection (EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Dunn, Henry O. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Dunny, G. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Dye, Joseph A. (Box 25, Folder 6)
        1892-1966
      - Dykes, Nathan Leonard (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Erb, Hollis Nancy (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Evans, Howard Edward (Box 25, Folder 9-16)
        1922-
        See also Papers 24-2-1870; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Fabricant, Catherine Grenci (Box 25, Folder 17)
        1919-2001
      - Fabricant, Julius (Box 25, Folder 18)
        19??-2011
        See also Oral History Collection 24-4-3349
      - Farnum, Cornelia E. (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Farrow, Brian R. H. (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Fewtrell, Clare Mary Sanders (Box 25, Folder 21)
        1948-
      - Field, Lincoln E. (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Fincher, Myron Gustin (Box 25, Folder 23-24)
        1898-1981
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-802; Memorial Statement
      - Fish, Pierre Augustine (Box 25, Folder 25)
        1865-1931
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-1677; Memorial Statement
      - Flanders, James A. (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Foerster, Sonia Hernandez (Box 25, Folder 27)
        1969-
      - Foote, Robert H. (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Fortune, Joanne (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Fox, Francis Henry (Box 25, Folder 30-33)
        1923-2015
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Frank, Diane (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Fregin, Frederick (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - French, Tracy Warren (Box 25, Folder 35)
        1951-2009
      - Frost, James Nathan (Box 25, Folder 36)
        1885-1949
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-1204; Memorial Statement
      - Fubini, Susan Lawson (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Fulmer, Curtis (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Gage, Simon Henry (Box 26, Folder 1)
        1851-1944
        See also Gage Family Papers 4937; Memorial Statement
      - Gans, Joseph H. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Gasteiger, Edgar L. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Geary, Jack Charles (Box 26, Folder 4)
        1920-1992
      - Gelzer, Anna (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Georgi, Jay Robert (Box 26, Folder 6)
        19??-2015
      - Georgi, Marion E. Schott (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Gilbert, Robert Owen (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Gillespie, James Howard (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
        See also Papers 24-2-3293
      - Gilman, Herbert Lester (Box 26, Folder 11)
        1895-1982
      - Gilmour, Robert Fulton, Jr. (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Gleed, Robin Desmond (Box 26, Folder 13)
        1953-
      - Glickman, Lawrence T. (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Goldstein, Richard S. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Gonzalez, Ruben Nestor (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Goodrich, Laura R. (Box 26, Folder 17)
        1965-
      - Gould, Willard Joseph, III "Jay" (Box 26, Folder 18)
        1949-
      - Graham, David Lee (Box 26, Folder 19)
        1939-
      - Griesemer, Richard A. (Box 26, Folder 20)
        1929-
      - Grohn, Yrjo Tapio (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Guan, Jun-Lin (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Guard, Charles L. (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Gunn, Teresa Monique (Box 26, Folder 24)
        1968-
      - Habel, Robert E. (Box 26, Folder 25)
        See also Oral History Collection 24-04-3349
      - Hackett, Mary Susan (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Hackett, Richard P. (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Hagan, William Arthur (Box 26, Folder 28)
        1893-1963
        See also Papers 24-1-482 and Memorial Statement
      - Hall, Charles (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Hansel, William (Box 26, Folder 30)
        1918-
      - Harkins, Daniel (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Harvey, Harold Jay (Box 26, Folder 32)
        1947-
      - Haussler, Kevin (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - Hayden, Charles Ernest (Box 26, Folder 34)
        1881-1948
      - Haynes, Nelson Bruce (Box 26, Folder 35)
        1926-
      - Henion, John D. (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Hermanson, John W. (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - Hill, Jonathan R. (Box 26, Folder 38)
      - Hillman, Robert Bryant (Box 26, Folder 39)
      - Hintz, Harold "Skip" (Box 26, Folder 40)
      - Hitchner, Stephen B. (Box 26, Folder 41)
      - Hopkins, Grant Sherman (Box 26, Folder 42)
        1865-1952
      - Hornbuckle, William E. (Box 26, Folder 43)
      - Holzinger, Edwin A. (Box 26, Folder 44)
      - Houpt, Katherine Albro (Box 26, Folder 45)
      - Houpt, Thomas Richard (Box 26, Folder 46)
        1925-2003
      - Hutt, Frederick Bruce (Box 26, Folder 47)
        1897-1991
      - Huxtable, Clive Rowan Ralston (Box 26, Folder 48)
        1940-
      - Jacobson, Richard H. (Box 26, Folder 49)
        1942-
      - Johnson, Seth Darwin (Box 26, Folder 50)
        1903-1975
        See also Alumni file 25-4-3326
      - Jubb, Kenneth V. (Box 26, Folder 51)
      - Kaderly, Robert (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Kahrs, Robert Frederick (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Kallfelz, Francis Anthony (Box 27, Folder 3)
        1938-
      - Kare, Morley R. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Kemen, Mathias John, Jr. (Box 27, Folder 5)
        1926-2009
      - Kenney, Robert M. (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Kern, Thomas J. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - King, John McKain (Box 27, Folder 8)
        1927-
      - Kingsbury, John M. (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Kirk, Robert Warren (Box 27, Folder 10-14)
        1922-2011
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-3372; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Kollias, George V., II (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Kotlikoff, Michael I. (Box 27, Folder 16)
        1951-
      - Kradel, David Charles (Box 27, Folder 17)
        1930-2006
      - Krook. Lennart P. (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Law, James (Box 27, Folder 19-22)
        1838-1921
        See also Paper 24-1-3329, Memorial Statement
      - Lee, David E. (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Lee, Kyu Myong (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Leibovitz, Louis (Box 27, Folder 24)
        1921-1998
      - Lein, Donald Henry (Box 27, Folder 25)
        1933-
      - Lengemann, Frederick W. (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Leonard, Ellis Pierson (Box 27, Folder 27-28)
        1904-1991
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-2645; Memorial Statement
      - Levine, Pincus Philip (Box 27, Folder 29)
        1907-1979
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection ( EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Levine, Roy A. (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Lewis, Robert M. (Box 27, Folder 31)
        1937-2011
      - Lindquist, Wesley (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Lindmark, Donald G. (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - Little, Thomas (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Loew, Ellis R. (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Loew, Franklin Martin (Box 27, Folder 36)
        1939-2003
      - Lowe, John Edward (Box 27, Folder 37)
        1935-
      - Looney, Andrea Lynn (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Lopez, Jorge (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - Lucio-Martinez, Benjamin (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Ludders, John William (Box 27, Folder 41)
        1944-
      - Lust, George (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - MacCauley, Alan (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - MacCoy, Douglas M. (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - MacLeod, James N. (Box 27, Folder 45)
        1959-
      - Manor, Danny (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Marmor, Michael (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - Marquis, Helene (Box 27, Folder 48)
      - Maylin, George A. (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - Mazza, Paul (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - McCashin, Fred B. (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - McClure, Robert C. (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - McDonough, Patrick L. (Box 27, Folder 53)
      - McDonough, Sean (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - McEntee, Kenneth B. (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
        1921-2005
      - McEntee, Margaret Colleen (Box 28, Folder 4)
        1955-
      - McGregor, Douglas D. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Melby, Edward Carlos, Jr. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Messick, Joanne B. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Meyers-Wallen, Vicki N. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Milks, Howard Jay (Box 28, Folder 9)
        1879-1954
      - Miller, Malcolm Eugene (Box 28, Folder 10)
        1909-1960
      - Miller, William H., Jr. (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Minor, Ronald R. (Box 28, Folder 12)
        1936-
      - Mizer, Linda (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Mohammed, Hussni O. (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Moise, Nancy Sydney (Box 28, Folder 15)
        1954-
      - Moore, Veranus Alva (Box 28, Folder 16)
        1859-1931
        See also Papers 24-1-119 and Memorial Statement
      - Morrisey, James K. (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Murphy, James M. (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Mutalib, Ahmed (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Nangeroni, Louis Lindo (Box 28, Folder 20)
        1918-1989
      - Naqi, Syed (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Nathanielsz, Peter W. (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
      - Nikitin, Alexander Yu (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Nixon, Alan J. (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Njaa, Bradley L. (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Noden, Drew M. (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Norcross, Neil L. (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Nowak, Linda M. (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - Nussbaum, Sidney Robert (Box 28, Folder 30)
        1924-1998
      - Nydam, Daryl V. (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - O'Connor, M. (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Olafson, Peter (Box 28, Folder 33-34)
        1897-1985
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-2234; Memorial Statement
      - Olander, Harvey J. (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - Osterrieder, Nikolaus (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - Oswald, Robert E. (Box 28, Folder 37)
      - Page, Rodney Lee (Box 28, Folder 38)
      - Panciera, Roger G. (Box 28, Folder 39)
      - Pauli, Benedict U. (Box 28, Folder 40)
      - Parrish, Colin Ross (Box 28, Folder 41)
      - Peckham, Malcolm Curtis (Box 28, Folder 42)
        1920-
      - Phemister, Robert D. (Box 28, Folder 43-45)
        See also Alumni File 24-4-3326
      - Playter, Robert (Box 28, Folder 46)